Radio Eye News Extra
Thank you very much!
Today's extra edition of Radio Eye News is titled "Personal Updates.
I'm going to share with you some news that's just for you.
It looks like we're going to get a new breed.
Okay, let's start with Rina-chan.
Yuukirina's cheating on her husband.
What? What?
You don't mind if I ask? The details?
Well, this is new information.
That's new information, isn't it?
I've already decided that onigiri is tuna mayo.
And Sanzel?
But recently
Yaki Onigiri (grilled rice ball) is now on sale
and they were being served.
I reached for it.
I thought, "No, no! I thought to myself
I said it a couple more times.
Oh, you cheater!
Tsunami was one way.
That's right.
I tried two tsunamis.
I said, "I've got to do it!" I'm sure you're thinking that tsunami will come back to me someday.
I'm sure it'll come back to me someday... from all the convenience stores in the country...
It's a cute little fight...
Ruri, please continue...
I've been addicted to random snacks, and random extras I've bought...
Recently, there was a Sanrio key chain that had a character that I liked, and I wanted to get her, so I got her, but I thought I might get the same one as her, so I got her, but she didn't come out.
I wanted to buy it, but my favorite character didn't appear on it, so I had to buy it again until my favorite character appears on it.
I'll have to keep buying them until they come out again.
I'll donate if I buy a pumpkin, but I'll donate if I buy a mocha, like, "Do you want that one?
I'll donate if I buy a pumpkin.
I've received a lot of gifts, but my guess is a character named Kogi Mun, so that's why I've received them.
I'm not sure if it's a random member or not, but I'm sure you've given it to her.
I like the penguin character, Mr. Tuxedo.
I like the character, and I'm working very hard on that girl right now.
I'm doing it with a sense of destiny. I hope it comes out soon.
I hope the hand-me-downs stop.
Well, so you told me your personal latest news, but...
By the way, I'm on Hashtag Radio a News.
I've been listening to the show since I was a kid and I love the atmosphere of the show.
I'm sure you'll be listening to it again in the future as well.
We have a live concert this weekend.
Yes, we'll be performing at Studio Freedom in Shibuya, where I'm a part of.
I'm going to be performing at Studio Freedom in Shibuya, Shibuya, where I'll be a part of the show.
I'm working on it now, and I'm sure you'll have different conversations with some of them and with others.
I hope you'll join us on Saturday, I'm looking forward to seeing you there!
Let's meet at Shibuya!
Thank you very much for your time.